In the street, a man greets us and invites
us into a shop.
Traditional Turkmen clothing is on sale
there.
I don't know if it's pretty.
I think I've already been very, very
strong on the horse.
It's not bad.
Is it OK?
I don't know, but he's dead laughing.
We soon find out that the man who stopped
us is not just a hat salesman.
With this one?
OK.
So...
No No It's you?
It's you.
Yes.
Could you show us?
Could you show
us?
Yes.
Could you show us?
I use it and I can easily access any
social media.
Yes, indeed.
But look.
YouTube.
It's incredible.
A blogger in a country where the internet
is virtually inaccessible and social
networking is banned, a mystery.
YouTube and WhatsApp.
He's keen to make a TikTok video with us.
I don't know the English name, but I'll
take it.
How many people are there?
Excuse me?
From France, yes.
France?
France.
Behind his smile, the man is hostile.
At the time, we didn't realise he was
laughing at us.
Me no ergek.
Me ergek.
Good hat.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you.
It was a pleasure.
Pleasure.
I will show you some more
This man, this man, this man, this man,
this man, this
man, this man, this man, this man, this
man, this man, According to the
dissidents,
this blogger is one of the few who can use
social networks in Turkmenistan.
His mission is to attack anyone who gets
in the way of the regime.
On his TikTok account, where he has
130,000 followers, we find the post where
he mocks us.
But above all, there are many violent
posts.
He attacks the most famous Turkmen
dissident in exile, Dursultan Taganova.
He imagines her face swollen.
Then he openly threatens her.